Bryce Murphy

Fort Wayne, Indiana, United States



bmurph0302@gmail.com



260.615.8118



linkedin.com/in/bryce-murphy-693304179

Summary

I am currently in my third year at Indiana Tech, pursuing a bachelor's degree in cybersecurity. I am a competing member of Indiana Tech's cyber defense and penetration testing team, which in the past year of CCDC earned first place in the state of Indiana, second place regionally and finished with a rank of 11th in the nation, and finished CPTC in global finals.

My specialty on Indiana Tech Cyber Warriors' roster is networking. In addition, I have three years of hands-on networking and security experience through my courses at Indiana Tech, and two years prior to that in the computer networking program at Anthis Career Center.

Aside from schoolwork, I have worked on and built computers, server systems, and networks on my own for more than ten years as a passion. I earned certifications in IT Fundamentals, CompTIA A+, eJPT, ISC2 Certified in Cybersecurity, and I am studying for various other certifications including CCNA, and aspiring to earn the OSCP.

My goal is to find an internship and/or an employment opportunity that would help me to gain experience and learn more within my field of study to help prepare me for success as a cybersecurity professional or penetration tester when I graduate.

IT Knowledge & Skills
TCP/IP networking and troubleshooting
Cisco IOS
Bash and PowerShell scripting
Unix Server Systems
Palo Alto Firewalls
Microsoft Windows administration
Troubleshooting hardware
Client service
SIEM & IDS systems
Managing help desk tickets

Experience



IT Security Intern

Ash Brokerage

May 2022 - Aug 2022 (4 months)

Responsibilities include:

Responding and investigating alerts in Rapid7 SIEM

Tracking risk and vulnerabilities in Insight VM

Managing security related tickets in help desk system

Applying and cleaning up security policies to our endpoint protections

Testing endpoint protections with controlled malware tests in "purple team" exercises

Other learning opportunities include:
Examining an enterprise firewall configuration
Imaging laptops for deployment
Using a ticketing system
General help desk work
Listening in on meetings reviewing other products to improve our security controls



Sweetwater

Sep 2021 - Sep 2022 (1 year 1 month)

Forklift Operator

Menards

Jun 2019 - Apr 2020 (11 months)

Education



D.S

Snider High School

Licenses & Certifications

(ISC) Certified in Cybersecurity - (ISC)²

eLearnSecurity Junior Penetration Tester

Skills

Scripting • Computer Repair • Help Desk Support • Computer Networking • Cybersecurity • Ethical Hacking